acceptsafe.com 2014-09-11

# 

                                                   PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is very important to AcceptSafe, LLC (Henceforward “AcceptSafe”, “We”, Us”). We want to make
your experience using our services on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use
the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This privacy
policy applies to http://www.acceptsafe.com owned and operated by AcceptSafe, LLC. The Company requests that
you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
We may, from time to time, offer links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on links to other
websites, you should read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.
Information Collection
AcceptSafe collects personal information from you when you submit a request for information or when you submit
your details for any other reason. The information, which is collected voluntarily, may include but is not limited to
business name, contact name, contact number, address, and email address.
Use of Information We Collect
We will use your information to fulfill any requests for information, provide products/services ordered by you or
process any other transactions authorized by you. Your personal information shall not be used for any other
purposes.
Access to Information
Access to the information we collect is limited to employees, affiliates, and AcceptSafe business relationships that
need the information to fulfill their business responsibilities. Users who provide information will be contacted either
by phone, mail or email. Your personal information will not be shared with nonaffiliated third parties, except in the
following circumstances:
          • In accordance with the AcceptSafe Privacy Policy
          • To facilitate and complete merchant-initiated or authorized transactions
          • To comply with federal, state and local laws, including credit reporting laws and card association rules
          • To combat fraud
When AcceptSafe engages vendors and other outside contractors, they are subject to our contractual requirements.
For purposes of credit reporting, verification and risk management, we may share information about you with third
parties as it relates to merchant services. We will also disclose information in response to a request issued by a court,
government agency or regulatory authority or as otherwise required by law.
Data Storage and Security
AcceptSafe understands the importance of security. We employ appropriate safeguards to protect user information.
These security measures are used to safeguard the personal information that we have under our control from
unauthorized access, improper use and disclosure, unauthorized destruction or accidental loss. However, we cannot
guarantee the protection of your personal data transmitted insecurely over the Internet. Our web site is theoretically
accessible by any user of the World Wide Web. You should be aware that when you disclose personal information
on the web that it may be collected by another user and may result in unsolicited messages from other Internet users.
                                                                                              Effective October 1, 2012

Further Information
If you have any questions or comments about the AcceptSafe Privacy Policy, please contact:
AcceptSafe, LLC
8800 East Chaparral Road
Suite 300
Scottsdale, AZ 85250
Telephone:
Toll-Free: 800.983-4289
Fax: 480.339.6728
Email: support@acceptsafe.com
                                                                                        Effective October 1, 2012
